<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Template</string>
    <string name="fetch_movie_info_error">Couldn\'t fetch movie data</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1419173978143843</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1419173978143843</string>
    <string name="plan_summaries">Plan summaries</string>
    <string name="take_pick_photo">Take or pick a photo</string>
    <string name="audio_permission_request">Allow our app to access you phrone data</string>
    <string name="voice_help">help</string>
    <string name="activities">Activities</string>
    <string name="title_activity_land_mark_map">Map</string>

    <string name="landmark_eiff">The Eiffel Tower is a wrought iron lattice tower on the Champ de Mars in Paris, France. It is named after the engineer Gustave Eiffel, whose company designed and built the tower.Constructed from 1887–89 as the entrance to the 1889 World\'s Fair, it was initially criticized by some of France\'s leading artists and intellectuals for its design, but it has become a global cultural icon of France and one of the most recognisable structures in the world. The Eiffel Tower is the most-visited paid monument in the world; 6.91 million people ascended it in 2015.</string>
    <string name="landmark_arc">The Arc de Triomphe de l\'Étoile is one of the most famous monuments in Paris, standing at the western end of the Champs-Élysées at the center of Place Charles de Gaulle, formerly named Place de l\'Étoile — the étoile or star of the juncture formed by its twelve radiating avenues.The Arc de Triomphe should not be confused with a smaller arch, the Arc de Triomphe du Carrousel, which stands west of the Louvre. The Arc de Triomphe honours those who fought and died for France in the French Revolutionary and Napoleonic Wars, with the names of all French victories and generals inscribed on its inner and outer surfaces. Beneath its vault lies the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier from World War I.</string>
    <string name="landmark_musee">The Louvre or the Louvre Museum is the world\'s largest museum and a historic monument in Paris, France. A central landmark of the city, it is located on the Right Bank of the Seine in the city\'s 1st arrondissement (district or ward). Approximately 38,000 objects from prehistory to the 21st century are exhibited over an area of 72,735 square metres (782,910 square feet). The Louvre is the world\'s second most visited museum after the Palace Museum in China, receiving more than 9.26 million visitors in 2014.</string>
    <string name="landmark_notre">Notre-Dame de Paris, also known as Notre-Dame Cathedral or simply Notre-Dame, is a medieval Catholic cathedral on the Île de la Cité in the fourth arrondissement of Paris, France. The cathedral is widely considered to be one of the finest examples of French Gothic architecture, and it is among the largest and most well-known church buildings in the world. The naturalism of its sculptures and stained glass are in contrast with earlier Romanesque architecture.</string>
    <string name="landmark_panth">The Panthéon is a building in the Latin Quarter in Paris. It was originally built as a church dedicated to St. Genevieve and to house the reliquary châsse containing her relics but, after many changes, now functions as a secular mausoleum containing the remains of distinguished French citizens. It is an early example of neo-classicism, with a façade modelled on the Pantheon in Rome, surmounted by a dome that owes some of its character to Bramante\'s Tempietto. Located in the 5th arrondissement on the Montagne Sainte-Geneviève, the Panthéon looks out over all of Paris. Designer Jacques-Germain Soufflot had the intention of combining the lightness and brightness of the Gothic cathedral with classical principles, but its role as a mausoleum required the great Gothic windows to be blocked.</string>


</resources>
